talkaboutmarriage.com 2013-04-19

# TalkAboutMarriage.com Privacy Policy

This website is **Talk About Marriage.  
**  
**Our postal address is**   
PO Box 850474  
New Orleans, LA 70185

We can be reached via e-mail at admin@talkaboutmarriage.com  
or by telephone at 1 (888) 354-8221.

  1. **Information Collected From All Visitors**
    * For each visitor to this website, our web server automatically collects the following types of information which are stored in secure log files on the server.
      * Type of user agent (web browser) used, software manufacture and version number. 
      * Type of operating system
      * Network location and IP address 
        * Can include country, city, state, region, county, or any other geographic data. 
        * Hostname 
        * Bandwidth (internet connection speed) 
      * Time of visit 
      * Pages visited 
      * Time spent on each page of the website 
      * Referring site statistics 
        * The website (URI) the user came through in order to arrive at this website (example: clicking on a hyperlink from Yahoo.com that took the user to this website) 
        * Search engine query used (example: typing in a phrase into a search engine like Google, and clicking on a link from that search engine) 
    * Visitors to this website who have javascript enabled are tracked using **Google Analytics**. Google Analytics collects the following types of information from users: 
      * Type of user agent (web browser) used, software manufacture and version number. 
      * Type of operating system 
      * Screen colors (color processing ability of the users screen) 
      * Javascript support 
      * Flash version 
      * Screen resolution 
      * Network location and IP address 
        * Can include country, city, state, region, county, or any other geographic data. 
        * Hostname 
        * Bandwidth (internet connection speed) 
      * Time of visit 
      * Pages visited 
      * Time spent on each page of the website 
      * Referring site statistics 
        * The website (URI) the user came through in order to arrive at this website (example: clicking on a hyperlink from Yahoo.com that took the user to this website) 
        * Search engine query used (example: typing in a phrase into a search engine like Google, and clicking on a link from that search engine) 
    * Google Analytics data is shared with Google. For more information on Google's Privacy Policies, visit: [ http://www.google.com/intl//privacypolicy.html](http://www.google.com/intl/privacypolicy.html)
    * **This data is primarily used to optimize our website for our visitors and search engines, however we will use this data for marketing purposes**. An example of how this data could be used for marketing purposes would be to tell potential advertisers how many visitors we get to the website, where our visitors come from, and how they arrive at our website. 
    * **This data DOES NOT include any personal identification information such as** : 
      * Names 
      * Phone Numbers 
      * Email Addresses 
      * Mailing Addresses 
      * Social Security Numbers 
      * Bank Account Numbers 
      * Credit Card Information 
  2. **Optional Voluntary Information**
    * We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users: 
      * Message boards/forums:  
Users of the site's Forums must register separately for this service in order to post messages, although they needn't register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to supply a username, password, date of birth and email address. Other types of personal information can be optionally entered into the user profile, and users have some control over who can see this information by adjusting their profile prvacy settings. All profileinformation is available to forum administrators and moderators. The profile privacy settings are available at the following URL: <http://talkaboutmarriage.com/profile.php?do=privacy>
      * Usage of message boards / forums:  
Any information a user posts on this website's message boards or forums should be considered public information that is viewable by anyone who comes to the site, regardless of where it is posted. Please visit our thread on anonymity to read about important considerations for posting on a public forum: <http://talkaboutmarriage.com/general-relationship-discussion/11063-important-message-about-anonymity-public-forums-like-talkaboutmarriage-com.html>
      * Usage of Private Messaging (PM's)  
Private messages sent on this forum are not viewable by anyone other than the recipient, unless the recipient "reports" the message using the "Report Private Message" link at the top right of the message. When a private message is "reported" using this feature, a copy of the message is sent to the site's administrator and moderators. 
      * "Email this page" Service:  
Our site users can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking "Email this Page". The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose. 
      * Polling:  
We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user other than the site administrator. TalkAboutMarriage.com may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users.
      * Children:  
Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. 
    * Suicidal / Homicidal threats or statements 
      * If a user makes suicidal or homicidal statements or threats on this website, we may report any identifiable information we have on the user to their internet service provider and / or 911.
  3. **With respect to cookies:** We use cookies to record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit.
  4. **With respect to Ad Servers:** To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of:  
<http://www.google.com/privacy.html>
    * **Google Adsense, their partners and other 3rd Party Advertisers**
      * Third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your users’ browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on this website.
      * List provided courtesy of [blogsblogsblogs.com](http://google-third-party-ads.blogsblogsblogs.com/)

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.  

  5. **With respect to security:** We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number, The DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at mgoldberger@the-dma.org, state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, state or local consumer protection office, The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202.FTC-HELP (202.382.4357) or electronically at http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm.
